Welcome to this Q&A video about the Mounspeak products and you had so many
questions here I am answering them. If you don't know them yet these are
anatomical gags they fill out your whole mouth you put your tongue inside and we
have different varieties. You can buy these from Mounspeak I will link it in
the description text and I also have a discount code so check that out. You can't
really breathe through your mouth because your whole mouth is filled out
but you still have a nose. You can wear them for several hours. My friend Frau Tagtraum
actually tried this and I think it was around about three to four hours. She
said it was no problem. Yes. I think they're comfortable to sleep with but I
would not recommend it for safety reasons. You have to choose true to your
size and if you're in doubt size down because if the gag is too big it can
affect your gag reflex. It also depends on the model. For example I know that
Frau Tagtorn prefers this one but I actually prefer this one because I have
a bit more choking problems with this and how it sits in my mouth but it's
completely individual. This is more locked in place due to the mouth guard
and I prefer that.
Not really because you have to put your
tongue inside and it is really much more than a mouth guard from boxing. It fills
out your whole mouth.
The tricky part actually is getting them inside your mouth. You have to squeeze a bit
but they're really soft and squishy and once they're in place it's totally comfortable and fine.
They're super easy to clean. It's medical grade silicone and you can simply wash them under warm
water. Maybe use very mild detergent and wash that away completely but it's fine after that.
The standard colors are purple, red and black but you can customize your own color and you can also
choose different colored hardware for the straps. I hope I could shed some light on these frequently
asked questions about the most big gags. If you have any further questions drop a comment down
below. Check out the discount code in the description text for 50% off and I will see
you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!